{
    "subject": "resource/New_York_Yankees",
    "predicate": "property/pennants",
    "object": "1999",
    "human_readable": "The New York Yankees won the pennant in 1999.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9487865567207336,
            "question": "Which team won the pennant in 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8952167630195618,
            "question": "What championship did the New York Yankees win in 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8724111318588257,
            "question": "Can you name another team that won the pennant in 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8699703216552734,
            "question": "When did the New York Yankees win the pennant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8132597208023071,
            "question": "In what year did the New York Yankees last win the pennant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6569938659667969,
            "question": "Who were some key players on the New York Yankees in 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43167486786842346,
            "question": "What is the significance of winning a pennant in baseball?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26331794261932373,
            "question": "What division did the New York Yankees play in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2590743899345398,
            "question": "Are there other sports teams called the Yankees?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2450280487537384,
            "question": "Is the New York Yankees a baseball team?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The New York Yankees won the pennant in 1999.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5137_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other sports teams called the Yankees?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5137_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What division did the New York Yankees play in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5137_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of winning a pennant in baseball?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5137_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5137_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5137_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5137_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5137_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5137_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5137_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5137_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5137_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5137_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5137_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to test more triples! \ud83d\ude0a  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document contains information about the 1999 season of the New York Yankees, stating that they \"kicked off the regular season in impressive fashion, triumphing in their initial four games and sustaining their high performance throughout the year\" and that they went on to win the World Series. This implies that they also won the pennant in 1999."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the performance of the New York Yankees in the 1999 season, including their record of 98-64 and their victory in the World Series. This supports the statement that The New York Yankees won the pennant in 1999."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}